Finding Aid for James J. Duderstadt Papers 1963-1997
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- Digital Documents 1986-1997, 2144 digital files 160.5 MB
  - Digital Images, circa 1996
    - Digital Images, 55 digital files (Box 1)
"Vision 2000 2.0," January 3, 1994, Write Files Series, [Digital Document], James J. Duderstadt Papers, Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan.
"Vision 2017 2.2," February 21, 1994, Write Files Series, [Digital Document], James J. Duderstadt Papers, Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan.
"Letter to Community," September 27, 1995, Write Files Series, [Digital Document], James J. Duderstadt Papers, Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan.
"Women 5.0," July 6, 1995, Position Papers Series, [Digital Document], James J. Duderstadt Papers, Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan.
"The Road Ahead," February 4, 1997, Position Papers Series, [Digital Document], James J. Duderstadt Papers, Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan.
Silberman, Eve. The U-M's Fast-moving New VP, Ann Arbor Observer [Michigan: Ann Arbor] October, 1986.
Related Material
Bentley Library Record Groups:
University of Michigan. College of Engineering.
University of Michigan. President.
University of Michigan. Provost and Vice President for Academic Affairs.
Internet Sources:
Researchers will find several related documents on the Internet. A search using the search engine Google [http://www.google.com] on January 25, 2002 retrieved numerous articles and images from The Detroit News, The University Record, and several full text speeches Duderstadt presented at other universities across the country.
The Millennium Institute
Information about James Duderstadt's current research on the future of education can be found online at: [http://milproj.ummu.umich.edu] (June 24, 1998 and January 25, 2002)